[
    {
        "Question": "Pete has 9 books. Ellen has 14 books. Who has the least number of books?",
        "Answer": "Pete"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Yoko has 11 pencils. Tony has 15 pencils. Who has the greater number of pencils?",
        "Answer": "Tony"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Sue eats 1 ear of corn. Her dad eats 2 ears of corn. How many do they eat altogether?",
        "Answer": 3.0
    },
    {
        "Question": "Carl buys 5 carrots. He has 3 more at home. How many carrots are there total?",
        "Answer": 8.0
    },
    {
        "Question": "Sam has 3 cats. Amy has 2. How many total cats?",
        "Answer": 5.0
    },
    {
        "Question": "The dog has 7 bones. He gets 3 more bones. How many bones altogether?",
        "Answer": 10.0
    },
    {
        "Question": "Doug and Mike play catch. Paul and Anna join them. How many children are there now?",
        "Answer": 4.0
    },
    {
        "Question": "9 children are at the party. 3 more children come. How many children are there now?",
        "Answer": 12.0
    },
    {
        "Question": "2 chickens are in the coop. 5 more chickens are in the yard. How many chickens altogether?",
        "Answer": 7.0
    },
    {
        "Question": "6 pigs are in the barn. 2 more pigs are in the mud. How many pigs in all?",
        "Answer": 8.0
    },
    {
        "Question": "There are 8 roses blooming on a bush. 2 more roses bloom the next day. How many total roses?",
        "Answer": 10.0
    },
    {
        "Question": "Mia picks 7 flowers. Tim picks 1 more and gives it to Mia. How many flowers does Mia have in all?",
        "Answer": 8.0
    },
    {
        "Question": "There are 4 cats in the yard. 3 more come. How many total cats?",
        "Answer": 7.0
    },
    {
        "Question": "There are 3 squirrels in the tree. 4 more come. How many altogether?",
        "Answer": 7.0
    },
    {
        "Question": "The cub eats 2 berries. Then he eats 8 more. How many berries does he eat in all?",
        "Answer": 10.0
    },
    {
        "Question": "4 cubs play. 4 more join them. How many cubs in all?",
        "Answer": 8.0
    },
    {
        "Question": "There are 8 peas on one plate. There are zero peas on the other plate. How many peas in all?",
        "Answer": 8.0
    },
    {
        "Question": "There are 5 apples in a bag. There are none in the other bag. How many total apples?",
        "Answer": 5.0
    },
    {
        "Question": "There are 0 leaves on the left page. There are 3 leaves on the right page. How many leaves in all?",
        "Answer": 3.0
    },
    {
        "Question": "There are 4 stickers on the top page and 0 stickers on the bottom page. How many stickers in all?",
        "Answer": 4.0
    },
    {
        "Question": "5 children sing. 3 children join in. How many children are singing altogether?",
        "Answer": 8.0
    },
    {
        "Question": "3 children dance. 2 children join in. How many total children are dancing?",
        "Answer": 5.0
    },
    {
        "Question": "Ben has 3 red balls and gets 5 green balls. How many balls does he have now?",
        "Answer": 8.0
    },
    {
        "Question": "Bill has 2 trucks. His friend, James came over with some more. Together they had 5 trucks. How many trucks did James bring over?",
        "Answer": 3.0
    },
    {
        "Question": "Jane caught 7 fish before she stopped to eat lunch. After lunch she caught some more. At the end of the day she had 9 fish. How many fish did she cathc after lunch?",
        "Answer": 2.0
    },
    {
        "Question": "I had 3 apples. My mom gave me some more. Then I had 10 apples. How many apples did my mom give me?",
        "Answer": 7.0
    },
    {
        "Question": "Bob caught 5 fish. John caught some more fish. They had 7 fish in all. How many fish did John catch?",
        "Answer": 2.0
    },
    {
        "Question": "Rachel and Lucy are playing with 5 trucks. If Rachel is playing with 2 of them, how many is Lucy playing with?",
        "Answer": 3.0
    },
    {
        "Question": "Jane had 9 fish at the end of the day. She had 7 fish before she ate lunch. How many fish did she catch after lunch?",
        "Answer": 2.0
    },
    {
        "Question": "Dad bought 6 shirts. The next day he returned some of them. Now he has 2 shirts. How many shirts did Dad return?",
        "Answer": 4.0
    },
    {
        "Question": "John had 3 strawberries. Then his friend gave him more fruit. Now John has 7 peices of fruit. How many pieces of fuit did John's friend give him?",
        "Answer": 4.0
    },
    {
        "Question": "There are 5 toy airplanes flying at the park. 1 went down and broke. How many airplances are stil flying?",
        "Answer": 4.0
    },
    {
        "Question": "I had 6 eggs from the store. 3 of them were cracked. How many eggs did I have that were not cracked?",
        "Answer": 3.0
    },
    {
        "Question": "Kate saw 8 cats playing in the grass. 3 went away to chase a mouse. How many cats remained in the grass?",
        "Answer": 5.0
    },
    {
        "Question": "There are 7 mango slices. 2 of them were eaten. How many mango slices are left to eat?",
        "Answer": 5.0
    },
    {
        "Question": "There were 9 kites flying in the park. 3 kites got caught in trees. How many kites were still flying?",
        "Answer": 6.0
    },
    {
        "Question": "There are 8 animals at the pond. 2 are big. The rest are small. How many are small?",
        "Answer": 6.0
    },
    {
        "Question": "There are 9 baseball players on the team. 7 are on the bench. How many are not on the bench?",
        "Answer": 2.0
    },
    {
        "Question": "Jill was given a total of 5 flowers for here birthday. She put 3 in one vase and the rest in another vase. How many did she put in the other vase?",
        "Answer": 2.0
    },
    {
        "Question": "Bill has 2 trucks. His friend, James came over with some more. Together they had 6 trucks. How many trucks did James bring over?",
        "Answer": 4.0
    },
    {
        "Question": "James caught 5 fish before she stopped to eat lunch. After lunch she caught some more. At the end of the day she had 9 fish. How many fish did she catch after lunch?",
        "Answer": 4.0
    },
    {
        "Question": "Kate made 7 cookies. Bill ate some. Now Kate had 5 cookies. How many cookies did Bill eat?",
        "Answer": 2.0
    },
    {
        "Question": "Deb blows up 9 balloons. Some ballons popped. 3 ballons are left. How many ballons popped?",
        "Answer": 6.0
    },
    {
        "Question": "4 children hop. 5 children join in. How many children are hopping in all?",
        "Answer": 9.0
    },
    {
        "Question": "3 children jump rope. 3 children join in. How many children are jumping rope?",
        "Answer": 6.0
    },
    {
        "Question": "Juan has 2 green dinosaurs. He also has 3 brown ones. How many dinosaurs does he have in all?",
        "Answer": 5.0
    },
    {
        "Question": "Lisa has 3 toy trucks. She also has 3 toy cars. How many toys does she have altogether?",
        "Answer": 6.0
    },
    {
        "Question": "Kay jumps 1 time. Gail jumps 5 times. How many times did they jump in all?",
        "Answer": 6.0
    },
    {
        "Question": "Sara buys 4 plums. John buys 2 plums. How many total plums did they buy?",
        "Answer": 6.0
    },
    {
        "Question": "3 friends are playing. 2 more friends join them. How many friends play?",
        "Answer": 5.0
    }
]